<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Govt Job Hunting</title>
	<atom:link href="https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 13:08:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/Government-Jobs.png</url>
	<title>Govt Job Hunting</title>
	<link>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>CELARITY WINS BEST OF STAFFING AWARDS FOR SERVICE EXCELLENCE</title>
		<link>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/celarity-wins-best-of-staffing-awards-for-service-excellence/</link>
					<comments>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/celarity-wins-best-of-staffing-awards-for-service-excellence/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 13:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/?p=30</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[BLOOMINGTON, MN – November 19, 2020&#160;–&#160;Celarity&#160;recently earned an award achieved by less than two percent of all staffing agencies in the U.S. and Canada, the 2020&#160;Best of Staffing Client Awards&#160;and&#160;The Best of Talent Awards&#160;for service excellence.&#160; ClearlyRated has awarded Celarity with the&#160;Best of Staffing Client Awards&#160;and&#160;The Best of Talent Awards&#160;(https://www.clearlyrated.com/staffing/mn-usa/bloomington-mn/celarity-bloomington-mn) for providing superior service to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.recruitment.guru/wp-content/uploads/2015/05/Government-Jobs-in-India.jpg" alt=""/></figure>



<p><strong>BLOOMINGTON, MN – November 19, 2020</strong>&nbsp;–&nbsp;<a href="https://www.celarity.com/best-staffing-recruiting-award/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Celarity</a>&nbsp;recently earned an award achieved by less than two percent of all staffing agencies in the U.S. and Canada, the 2020&nbsp;<em>Best of Staffing Client Awards&nbsp;</em>and&nbsp;<em>The Best of Talent Awards</em>&nbsp;for service excellence.&nbsp;</p>



<div class="wp-block-columns alignwide">
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:100%"></div>
</div>



<p>ClearlyRated has awarded Celarity with the&nbsp;<em>Best of Staffing Client Awards&nbsp;</em>and&nbsp;<em>The Best of Talent Awards</em>&nbsp;(<a href="https://www.clearlyrated.com/staffing/mn-usa/bloomington-mn/celarity-bloomington-mn" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://www.clearlyrated.com/staffing/mn-usa/bloomington-mn/celarity-bloomington-mn</a>) for providing superior service to clients and candidates.&nbsp;</p>



<p>In partnership with presenting sponsor, CareerBuilder, and gold sponsors Indeed and Glassdoor,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.clearlyrated.com/staffing" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ClearlyRated’s Best of Staffing® Award</a>&nbsp;winners have proven to be industry leaders in service quality based&nbsp;entirely on ratings provided by their&nbsp;clients and candidates.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Each member of our team works to build personal, lasting relationships with our contractors, candidates, and clients.” Said Robert Arnold, Chief Fulfillment &amp; Finance Officer. “We feel very honored that our community recognizes our effort to fulfill our core mission of&nbsp;<em>Creating Happy Careers</em>.”&nbsp;</p>



<p>Celarity received satisfaction scores of 9 or 10 out of 10 from 84.4% of their placed job candidates, significantly higher than the industry’s average of 45%. On average, clients of winning agencies are 3.3 times more likely to be completely satisfied, and candidates who have been placed by winning agencies are 1.7 times more likely to be completely satisfied with the services provided compared to those working with non-winning agencies.&nbsp;</p>



<p>“Now more than ever, it is important for staffing firms to deliver consistently remarkable experiences to the clients and talent they work with,” said ClearlyRated’s CEO Eric Gregg. “This year’s Best of Staffing winners have shown their commitment to exceptional service, committing to not only measuring satisfaction but taking action on the feedback. I couldn’t be more proud to showcase these industry leaders alongside feedback from their actual clients and candidates on ClearlyRated.com and applaud them for their commitment to making improvements at their respective firms!”</p>



<p>Celarity received over 25 verified client ratings earning 5 out of 5 stars. “We believe these awards illustrate our team living out our company values of helpfulness, professionalism, and passion.” said Arnold. “Congratulations to the entire Celarity team and thank you to our consultants, candidates, and clients.”</p>



<h4><strong>About Celarity</strong></h4>



<h4>Celarity is a&nbsp;marketing, creative, and digital staffing and recruiting agency. Regardless of the type of organization, large or small, or what industry you service, Celarity has placed talent in a similar setting. They’re proud to have helped over 600 companies with over 5,000 talent needs.</h4>



<h4><strong>About ClearlyRated</strong></h4>



<p>Rooted in satisfaction&nbsp;research for professional service firms,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.clearlyrated.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ClearlyRated</a>&nbsp;utilizes a Net Promoter Score survey program to help professional service firms&nbsp;measure their service experience, build online reputation, and differentiate on service quality.&nbsp;Learn more at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.clearlyrated.com/solutions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">https://www.clearlyrated.com/solutions/</a>.</p>



<h4><strong>About Best of Staffing</strong></h4>



<p><a href="https://www.clearlyrated.com/staffing" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ClearlyRated’s Best of Staffing® Award</a>&nbsp;is the only award in the U.S. and Canada that recognizes staffing agencies that have proven superior service quality based entirely on ratings provided by their clients and job candidates. Award winners are showcased by city and area of expertise on ClearlyRated.com – an online business directory that helps buyers of professional services find service leaders and vet prospective firms – based exclusively on validated client and talent ratings and testimonials.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/celarity-wins-best-of-staffing-awards-for-service-excellence/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Handle Job Rejection</title>
		<link>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/how-to-handle-job-rejection/</link>
					<comments>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/how-to-handle-job-rejection/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 11:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Getting rejected from a job opportunity you’re excited about can be detrimental to&#160;your&#160;confidence in your job search. The application and interview stages are&#160;usually quite a process and no matter where you are in that process, if you get rejected, it’s tough. Many candidates internalize this and it can majorly affect the&#160;motivation to jump back into [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://www.celarity.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/LeadImagehow_to_deal_with_job_rejection-570x427.png" alt=""/></figure>



<p>Getting rejected from a job opportunity you’re excited about can be detrimental to&nbsp;your&nbsp;confidence in your job search. The application and interview stages are&nbsp;usually quite a process and no matter where you are in that process, if you get rejected, it’s tough. Many candidates internalize this and it can majorly affect the&nbsp;motivation to jump back into your search. So, how do you overcome the rejection in a job search?</p>



<p><strong>Reflect on the experience</strong><br>When you experience a ‘no’ in your job search,&nbsp;take the opportunity to turn it into a learning experience. Is there anything you wish you would have done differently throughout the hiring process? Did you learn anything about yourself? i.e. interview skills you need to work on, job responsibilities you do/don’t want to do. Take what you learned throughout the process and work on applying that to your next interview experience and become an even stronger candidate. Did the hiring manager give you any feedback? Use that too!</p>



<p><strong>No bridge burning</strong><br>One of the most difficult things to do when you’ve been rejected by an employer is to move on from the experience and not let it get you down. It’s easy to be angry and bad-mouth the employer, but you want to make sure you’re smart and avoid burning any bridges for future employment opportunities. If the company took time to interview you and included you in their pool of candidates, they saw you as a viable option and could possibly consider you again if the position opens. You could also&nbsp;potentially reach back out to the connections you made for networking purposes.</p>



<p><strong>Fuel the fire</strong><br>Your natural instinct might be to give up and lose momentum, don’t do this! Use the rejection from the opportunity and let it motivate you even more! As mentioned before, use this as a learning experience to become the best candidate you can be. Get back out there and don’t let one or even a few rejections get you down, your perfect opportunity could be on it’s way.Getting turned down by an opportunity you were excited about is tough no matter what but if you handle it in the right way, it can end up benefiting you in the long run!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/how-to-handle-job-rejection/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 11:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://sohelmalek.github.io/Govtjob/2020/12/22/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
